{
    "subject": "resource/Equestrian_at_the_1924_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Team_jumping",
    "predicate": "ontology/silverMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Werner_Stuber",
    "human_readable": "Werner Stuber was a silver medalist in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8471687436103821,
            "question": "At which Summer Olympics did Werner Stuber compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7917729020118713,
            "question": "Who was Werner Stuber?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7713401317596436,
            "question": "What year did Werner Stuber win his medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6946961283683777,
            "question": "In what sport did Werner Stuber earn a medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6854088306427002,
            "question": "What color medal did Werner Stuber win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6659170985221863,
            "question": "What was the name of the event in which Werner Stuber competed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179445385932922,
            "question": "Was Werner Stuber competing individually or as part of a team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5961372256278992,
            "question": "What type of competition did Werner Stuber participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43382900953292847,
            "question": "What distinguishes a silver medalist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21878944337368011,
            "question": "Which event requires 'team jumping'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Werner Stuber was a silver medalist in team jumping at the 1924 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6259_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What distinguishes a silver medalist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6259_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of competition did Werner Stuber participate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6259_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Werner Stuber competing individually or as part of a team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6259_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6259_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports that Werner Mortimer Stuber, along with his horse Girandole, won the silver medal as part of the Swiss team in the team jumping competition during the 1924 Summer Olympics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}